A Guide to the Episcopal Diocese of Southwestern Virginia 1905-1990
Digital Libraries and Archives, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Bristol--Emmanuel (17) 1943 (Box-folder 67-7)
- Buchanan--Trinity (20) 1943 (Box-folder 67-8)
- Buena Vista--Christ (21) 1943 (Box-folder 67-9)
- Callaway--St. Peter's (22) 1943 (Box-folder 67-10)
- Christiansburg--St. Thomas (23) 1943 (Box-folder 67-11)
- Clifford--St. Mark's (24) 1943 (Box-folder 67-12)
- Clifton Forge--St. Andrew's (25) 1943 (Box-folder 67-13)
- Covington--Emmanuel (27) 1943 (Box-folder 67-14)
- Covington--Grace Chapel (28) 1943 (Box-folder 67-15)
- Dante/Honey Branch--St. Mark's Mission (28A, 29, 40A) 1943 (Box-folder 67-16)
- Dante--St. Mark's (29) 1943 (Box-folder 67-17)
- Dante--St. Mark's--history (29) 1943 (Box-folder 67-18)
- Ferrum--St. John's (33) 1943 (Box-folder 67-19)
- Fincastle--St. Mark's (34) 1943 (Box-folder 67-20)
- Folly Mills--Good Shepherd (35) 1943 (Box-folder 67-21)
- Forest--St. Stephen's (37) 1943 (Box-folder 67-22)
- Gladys--Christ Church (39) 1943 (Box-folder 67-23)
- Glasgow--St. John's (40) 1943 (Box-folder 67-24)
- Hot Springs--St. Luke's (41) 1943 (Box-folder 67-25)
- Lexington--R.E. Lee Memorial (44) 1943 (Box-folder 67-26)
- Lynchburg--Good Shepherd (46); Lynchburg--Grace Memorial (47); Lynchburg--St. John's (48) 1943 (Box-folder 67-27)
- Lynchburg--St. Paul's (49); Madison Heights--Emmanuel (50); Marion--Christ Church (51) 1943 (Box-folder 67-28)
- Martinsville--Christ Church (52) 1943 (Box-folder 67-29)
- Martinsville--St. Paul's (52A); Massies Mill--Grace (53); Montvale--St. Mark's (55) 1943 (Box-folder 67-30)
- Nora--St. Stephen's (57); Norton--All Saints (58); Norwood--Christ Church (59) 1943 (Box-folder 67-31)
- Pearisburg--Christ Church (60); Pedlar Mills--St. Luke's (61); Pocahontas--Christ Church (62) 1943 (Box-folder 67-32)
- Pulaski--Christ Church (64) 1943 (Box-folder 67-33)
- Radford--Grace Chruch (65) 1943 (Box-folder 67-34)
- Richlands--Trinity (66); Roanoke--Christ Church (67); Roanoke--St. John's (68) 1943 (Box-folder 67-35)
- Roanoke--St. John's--Men's Club (68A) 1943 (Box-folder 67-36)
- Roanoke--St. Luke's (69); Roanoke--St. Luke's--proposal of Y Hutsona (69A); Roanoke--St. Peter's (70) 1943 (Box-folder 67-37)
- Roanoke--St. Peter's (70) 1943 (Box-folder 67-38)
- Rocky Mount--Trinity (71); St. Paul--Grace House (72) 1943 (Box-folder 67-39)
- Salem--St. Paul's (74); Saltville--St. Paul's (75); Schuyler--Christ Church (76) 1943 (Box-folder 67-40)
- Splashdam--Mission (78); Staunton--Emmanuel (79); Staunton--Trinity (80) 1943 (Box-folder 67-41)
- Sweet Briar College (81); Tazewell--Stras Memorial (82); Waynesboro--St. John's (84) 1943 (Box-folder 67-42)
- Wytheville--St. John's (85); A--general (87) 1943 (Box-folder 67-43)
- B--general (88); C--general (89); E--general (91) 1943 (Box-folder 67-44)
- F--general (92); G--general (93); H--general (94) 1943 (Box-folder 67-45)
- I--general (95); K--general (97); L--general (98) 1943 (Box-folder 67-46)
- M--general (99); N--general (100); O--general (101) 1943 (Box-folder 67-47)
- P-Q--general (102); R--general (103); S--general (104) 1943 (Box-folder 67-48)
- T--general (105); U-V--general (106); W--general (107) 1943 (Box-folder 67-49)
- Altar Guilds (108A); American Church Building Fund (109); Army and Navy Commission (112) 1943 (Box-folder 67-50)
- The Bishop's Council Address (117) 1943 (Box-folder 67-51)
- Boys Home, Inc. (119) 1943 (Box-folder 67-52)
- Chancellor of the Diocese (120); Chaplin, Paul (120A); Church School Lenten Offering (122) 1943 (Box-folder 67-53)
- Box 68 1943
- Church Pension Fund (121) 1943 (Box-folder 68-1)
- Church Pension Fund--re. individual clergymen--closed (121C) 1943 (Box-folder 68-2)
- Church Society for College Work (122B) 1943 (Box-folder 68-3)
- Clergy Conference (124); Clergy--list and general (125); Consent (129) 1943 (Box-folder 68-4)
- Council--clerical support (133) 1943 (Box-folder 68-5)
- Council--election and credentials (136) 1943 (Box-folder 68-6)
- Council--general (138) 1943 (Box-folder 68-7)
- Council--general (138); Council--Hospitality Committee (139); Council--minutes (141) 1943 (Box-folder 68-8)
- Parochial Reports (144) 1943 (Box-folder 68-9)
- Council--program (145) 1943 (Box-folder 68-10)
- Council--reports (146) 1943 (Box-folder 68-11)
- Council--secretary (148) 1943 (Box-folder 68-12)
- Depositions (151); Diocesan Records (154) 1943 (Box-folder 68-13)
- Diocesan Office (153) 1943 (Box-folder 68-14)
- Episcopal High School (156); Episcopal Residence (157) 1943 (Box-folder 68-15)
- Examining Chaplains (159); Department of Promotion--field section (162A) 1943 (Box-folder 68-16)
- Executive Board--secretary (161) 1943 (Box-folder 68-17)
- Treasurer's Statement--diocesan expense and Field Department expense (164) 1943 (Box-folder 68-18)
- Executive Board--Department of Finance (164); Executive Board--Department of Religious Education 1943 (Box-folder 68-19)
- Executive Board--Department of Social Service (167); Executive Board--general (168) 1943 (Box-folder 68-20)
- Federal Council of Churches (170) 1943 (Box-folder 68-21)
- Forward Movement--forward in service (172) 1943 (Box-folder 68-22)
- General Convention--Cleveland, October 2, 1943 (174) 1943 (Box-folder 68-23)
- General Convention--Thomas A. Scott File (174A) 1943 (Box-folder 68-24)
- Good Friday Offering (178) 1943 (Box-folder 68-25)
- House of Bishops (179A); Reverend E.W. Hughes Fund (179A) 1943 (Box-folder 68-26)
- Industrial Work (179A); Journal--minutes (185) 1943 (Box-folder 68-27)
- Insurance (180) 1943 (Box-folder 68-28)
- Journal--publisher (186) 1943 (Box-folder 68-29)
- Koci, Joseph Charles (186B); Letters Dimissory (191) 1943 (Box-folder 68-30)
- Laymen's League--Thomas A. Scott File (189A) 1943 (Box-folder 68-31)
- Living Church--paper (193) 1943 (Box-folder 68-32)
- National Council--Department of Domestic Missions (198) 1943 (Box-folder 68-33)
- National Council--Department of Promotion--including Field and Publicity (202); National Council--miscellaneous (203) 1943 (Box-folder 68-34)
- National Council--President (205) 1943 (Box-folder 68-35)
- National Council--Treasurer (206) 1943 (Box-folder 68-36)
- Annual Diocesan report and relevant correspondence (206A) 1943 (Box-folder 68-37)
- National Council--Women's Auxiliary (207) 1943 (Box-folder 68-38)
- Bishop Phillips--personal (Folder 1 of 2, 209C) 1943 (Box-folder 68-39)
- Bishop Phillips--personal (Folder 2 of 2, 209C) 1943 (Box-folder 68-40)
- Phillips, H.D.--special (209D) 1943 (Box-folder 68-41)
- Province of Washington--deaf mutes (211); Province of Washington--general (212) 1943 (Box-folder 68-42)
- Provincial Advanced Conference--Sweet Briar College (212A) 1943 (Box-folder 68-43)
- Receipts (215) 1943 (Box-folder 68-44)
- Box 69 1943-44
- Jennie Roach (215A); Russell, Francis R.--accepted as a postulant January 17, 1943 (215C) 1943 (Box-folder 69-1)
- St. Paul's School--Lawrenceville (216); Shamhart, L. Roper--Covington--admitted June 8, 1943--recommended by Rev. Richard Trapnell, March 22, 1943 (217A) 1943 (Box-folder 69-2)
- Southwestern Episcopalian (219) 1943 (Box-folder 69-3)
- Standing Committee (221) 1943 (Box-folder 69-4)
- Stuart Hall (222) 1943 (Box-folder 69-5)
- Stuart Hall--re. new principal (222) 1943 (Box-folder 69-6)
- Stuart Hall Trustees--meeting April 17th (222A) 1943 (Box-folder 69-7)
- Summer Schools--outside the diocese (223) 1943 (Box-folder 69-8)
- Theological Seminary of Virginia (224) 1943 (Box-folder 69-9)
- Treasurer of Diocese (225) 1943 (Box-folder 69-10)
- Trustees of Diocese (226) 1943 (Box-folder 69-11)
- United Thank Offering (227) 1943 (Box-folder 69-12)
- United Thank Offering--workers (227) 1943 (Box-folder 69-13)
- Vestries (228) 1943 (Box-folder 69-14)
- Virginia Episcopal School (229) 1943 (Box-folder 69-15)
- Virginia Episcopal School--prospective applicants (229) 1943 (Box-folder 69-16)
- Virginia Episcopal School--Dr. George L. Barton, Jr. as new headmaster (229) 1943 (Box-folder 69-17)
- Virginia Episcopal School--board meeting (229) 1943 (Box-folder 69-18)
- Virginia Episcopal School--material (229A) 1943 (Box-folder 69-19)
- Visitations (230) 1943 (Box-folder 69-20)
- The Witness (231) 1943 (Box-folder 69-21)
- Women's Auxiliary--diocesan (232) 1943 (Box-folder 69-22)
- Women's Auxiliary--outside the diocese (233) 1943 (Box-folder 69-23)
- Women Workers--general (234) 1943 (Box-folder 69-24)
- Women Workers--general (234) 1943 (Box-folder 69-25)
- Young People (235) 1943 (Box-folder 69-26)
- Young People's Conference (235A) 1943 (Box-folder 69-27)
- Young Peoples Conference--registrations (235B) 1943 (Box-folder 69-28)
- Episcopal High School (156) 1943-44 (Box-folder 69-29)
- Gus Hall of Splashdam (178 1/2) 1943-44 (Box-folder 69-30)
- Laymen's League (189) 1943-44 (Box-folder 69-31)
- Clergy 1944 (Box-folder 69-32)
- Council Reports--May 16-17 1944 (Box-folder 69-33)
- Koch, Reverend Arthur E.--correspondence with Bishop Phillips 1944 (Box-folder 69-34)
- St. John's Church School--Treasurer's Report 1944 (Box-folder 69-35)
- St. Paul RFD--Grace House and Mr. Tyler's correspondence 1944 (Box-folder 69-36)
- Abingdon--St. Thomas (2) 1944 (Box-folder 69-37)
- Abingdon--St. Thomas--history (2) 1944 (Box-folder 69-38)
- Altavista--St. Peter's (5) 1944 (Box-folder 69-39)
- Amherst--Ascension (6) 1944 (Box-folder 69-40)
- Amherst--St. Paul's Mission (7) 1944 (Box-folder 69-41)
- Arrington--Trinity (9) 1944 (Box-folder 69-42)
- Bedford--St. John's (10) 1944 (Box-folder 69-43)
- Bedford--St. Phillip's (11) 1944 (Box-folder 69-44)
- Big Stone Gap--Christ Church (13) 1944 (Box-folder 69-45)
- Blacksburg--Christ (14) 1944 (Box-folder 69-46)
- Bluefield--St. Mary's (15) 1944 (Box-folder 69-47)
- Boonsboro--Trinity (16) 1944 (Box-folder 69-48)
- Bristol--Emmanuel (17) 1944 (Box-folder 69-49)
- Buena Vista--Christ Church (21) 1944 (Box-folder 69-50)
- Callaway--St. Peter's (22) 1944 (Box-folder 69-51)
- Christiansburg--St. Thomas (23) 1944 (Box-folder 69-52)
- Clifford--St. Mark's (24) 1944 (Box-folder 69-53)
- Clifton Forge--St. Andrew's (25) 1944 (Box-folder 69-54)
- Covington--Emmanuel (27) 1944 (Box-folder 69-55)
- Dante--St. Mark's (29) 1944 (Box-folder 69-56)
- Ferrum--St. John's-in-the-mountains--history (30) 1944 (Box-folder 69-57)
- Evington--Good Shepherd (32) 1944 (Box-folder 69-58)
- Box 70 1944
- Ferrum--St. John's (33) 1944 (Box-folder 70-1)
- Fincastle--St. Mark's (34) 1944 (Box-folder 70-2)
- Folly Mills--Good Shepherd (35) 1944 (Box-folder 70-3)
- Forest--St. Stephen's (37) 1944 (Box-folder 70-4)
- Glasgow--St. John's (40) 1944 (Box-folder 70-5)
- Honey Branch Mission (40A) 1944 (Box-folder 70-6)
- Hot Springs--St. Luke's (41) 1944 (Box-folder 70-7)
- Lexington--R.E. Lee Memorial (44) 1944 (Box-folder 70-8)
- Lynchburg--Good Shepherd (46) 1944 (Box-folder 70-9)
- Lynchburg--Grace Memorial (47) 1944 (Box-folder 70-10)
- Lynchburg--St. John's (48) 1944 (Box-folder 70-11)
- Lynchburg--St. Pauls' (49) 1944 (Box-folder 70-12)
- Madison Heights--Emmanuel (50) 1944 (Box-folder 70-13)
- Marion--Christ Church (51) 1944 (Box-folder 70-14)
- Martinsville--Christ Church (52) 1944 (Box-folder 70-15)
- Martinsville--St. Paul's Mission (52A) 1944 (Box-folder 70-16)
- Massies Mill--Grace Church (53) 1944 (Box-folder 70-17)
- Norton--All Saints (58) 1944 (Box-folder 70-18)
- Norton--All Saints--rectory (58) 1944 (Box-folder 70-19)
- Pearisburg--Christ Church (600) 1944 (Box-folder 70-20)
- Pedlar Mills--St. Luke's (61) 1944 (Box-folder 70-21)
- Pocahontas--Christ Church (62) 1944 (Box-folder 70-22)
- Pulaski--Christ Church (64) 1944 (Box-folder 70-23)
- Radford--Grace Church (65) 1944 (Box-folder 70-24)
- Richlands--Trinity (66) 1944 (Box-folder 70-25)
- Roanoke--Christ Church (67) 1944 (Box-folder 70-26)
- Roanoke--St. John's (68) 1944 (Box-folder 70-27)
- Roanoke--St. John's--Men's Club (68A) 1944 (Box-folder 70-28)
- Roanoke--St. Peter's (70) 1944 (Box-folder 70-29)
- Rocky Mount--Trinity (71) 1944 (Box-folder 70-30)
- St. Paul--Grace House (72) 1944 (Box-folder 70-31)
- Salem--St. Paul's (74) 1944 (Box-folder 70-32)
- Splashdam--Good Shepherd (78) 1944 (Box-folder 70-33)
- Staunton--Emmanuel (79) 1944 (Box-folder 70-34)
- Staunton--Trinity (80) 1944 (Box-folder 70-35)
- Tazewell--Stras Memorial (82) 1944 (Box-folder 70-36)
- Waynesboro--St. John's (84) 1944 (Box-folder 70-37)
- Wytheville--St. John's (85) 1944 (Box-folder 70-38)
- B--general (88) 1944 (Box-folder 70-39)
- C--general (89) 1944 (Box-folder 70-40)
- I--general (95) 1944 (Box-folder 70-41)
- M--general (99) 1944 (Box-folder 70-42)
- P-Q--general (102) 1944 (Box-folder 70-43)
- S--general (104) 1944 (Box-folder 70-44)
- Boys' Home, Inc. (119) 1944 (Box-folder 70-45)
- Church Pension Fund (121) 1944 (Box-folder 70-46)
- Church Pension Fund--re. individual clergymen--closed (121C) 1944 (Box-folder 70-47)
- Church Society for College Work (122B) 1944 (Box-folder 70-48)
- Clergy Conference (124) 1944 (Box-folder 70-49)
- Consents (129) 1944 (Box-folder 70-50)
- Council--clerical support (133) 1944 (Box-folder 70-51)
- Council--general (138) 1944 (Box-folder 70-52)
- Parochial Reports (144) 1944 (Box-folder 70-53)
- Council--rules of order (146A) 1944 (Box-folder 70-54)
- Council--Secretary (148) 1944 (Box-folder 70-55)
- Depositions (151) 1944 (Box-folder 70-56)
- Diocesan Office (153) 1944 (Box-folder 70-57)
- Diocesan Office (153) 1944 (Box-folder 70-58)
- Diocesan Records (154) 1944 (Box-folder 70-59)
- Elliot Addressing Machine (155A) 1944 (Box-folder 70-60)
- Examining Chaplains (159) 1944 (Box-folder 70-61)
- Field Department--pledges (163) 1944 (Box-folder 70-62)
- Executive Board--Department of Finance (164) 1944 (Box-folder 70-63)
- Treasurer's Statement--diocesan expenses and Field Department (164) 1944 (Box-folder 70-64)
- Executive Board--Department of Promotion (165) 1944 (Box-folder 70-65)
- Executive Board--general (168) 1944 (Box-folder 70-66)
- General Convention (174) 1944 (Box-folder 70-67)
- House of Bishops (179A) 1944 (Box-folder 70-68)
- Industrial Work (179B) 1944 (Box-folder 70-69)
- Insurance (180) 1944 (Box-folder 70-70)
- Laymen's League (189) 1944 (Box-folder 70-71)
- Laymen's League--Thomas A. Scott File (189A) 1944 (Box-folder 70-72)
- Letters Dimissory (191) 1944 (Box-folder 70-73)
- National Council--Home Department (198) 1944 (Box-folder 70-74)
- Mission Workers' Conference (196 1/2) 1944 (Box-folder 70-75)
- National Council--general (201) 1944 (Box-folder 70-76)
- National Council--President (204) 1944 (Box-folder 70-77)
- National Council--Speakers' Bureau (205B) 1944 (Box-folder 70-78)
- Box 71 1944-45
- National Council--Treasurer (206) 1944 (Box-folder 71-1)
- National Council--Women's Auxiliary (207) 1944 (Box-folder 71-2)
- Bishop Phillips--personal (209C) 1944 (Box-folder 71-3)
- Province of Washington--general (212) 1944 (Box-folder 71-4)
- Provincial Advanced Conference--Sweet Briar (212A) 1944 (Box-folder 71-5)
- Province of Washington--synod (213) 1944 (Box-folder 71-6)
- St. Paul's School--Lawrenceville (216) 1944 (Box-folder 71-7)
- Southwestern Episcopalian (219) 1944 (Box-folder 71-8)
- Standing Committee (221) 1944 (Box-folder 71-9)
- Stuart Hall (222) 1944 (Box-folder 71-10)
- Stuart Hall (222) 1944 (Box-folder 71-11)
- Stuart Hall--special--the Bishop (222A) 1944 (Box-folder 71-12)
- Theological Seminary (224) 1944 (Box-folder 71-13)
- Treasurer of Diocese (225) 1944 (Box-folder 71-14)
- Treasurer of Diocese (225) 1944 (Box-folder 71-15)
- Treasurer of Diocese (225) 1944 (Box-folder 71-16)
- Trustees of Diocese (226) 1944 (Box-folder 71-17)
- United Thank Offering (227) 1944 (Box-folder 71-18)
- Vestries (228) 1944 (Box-folder 71-19)
- Virginia Council of Churches (228B) 1944 (Box-folder 71-20)
- Virginia Episcopal School (229) 1944 (Box-folder 71-21)
- Whiting, Robert W. of High Point, North Carolina (230A) 1944 (Box-folder 71-22)
- Women's Auxiliary--diocesan (232) 1944 (Box-folder 71-23)
- Women's Auxiliary--outside of diocese (233) 1944 (Box-folder 71-24)
- Women Workers--general (234) 1944 (Box-folder 71-25)
- Young People (235) 1944 (Box-folder 71-26)
- Young People (235) 1944 (Box-folder 71-27)
- Roanoke--St. Peter's (70) 1944-45 (Box-folder 71-28)
- Sweet Briar (81) 1944-45 (Box-folder 71-29)
- P-Q--general (102) 1944-45 (Box-folder 71-30)
- Birthday Thank Offering (116) 1944 (Box-folder 71-31)
- The Living Church (193) 1944-45 (Box-folder 71-32)
- Reorganization of Evans House Staff 1944-46 (Box-folder 71-33)
- Clergy 1945 (Box-folder 71-34)
- Executive Board--March 15--minutes 1945 (Box-folder 71-35)
- Berkeley, Alfred Rives, Reverend, D.D., of St. John's-- Roanoke 1945 (Box-folder 71-36)
- Block, Karl Morgan, Right Reverend, D.D., of the Diocese of California--former rector of St. John's in Roanoke 1945 (Box-folder 71-37)
- St. John's Church School--Treasurer's report 1945 (Box-folder 71-38)
- Trustees of the Diocese--The Bishop's Folder 1945 (Box-folder 71-39)
- Abingdon--St. Thomas (2) 1945 (Box-folder 71-40)
- Air Point (3) 1945 (Box-folder 71-41)
- Altavista--St. Peter's (5) 1945 (Box-folder 71-42)
- Amherst--Ascension (6) 1945 (Box-folder 71-43)
- Amherst--St. Paul's Mission (7) 1945 (Box-folder 71-44)
- Appalachia (8) 1945 (Box-folder 71-45)
- Arrington--Trinity--letters dimissory (9) 1945 (Box-folder 71-46)
- Arrinton--Trinity (9) 1945 (Box-folder 71-47)
- Bedford--St. John's (10) 1945 (Box-folder 71-48)
- Bedford--St. Philip's (11) 1945 (Box-folder 71-49)
- Big Island--St. Thomas (12) 1945 (Box-folder 71-50)
- Big Stone Gap--Christ (13) 1945 (Box-folder 71-51)
- Blacksburg--Christ (14) 1945 (Box-folder 71-52)
- Bluefield--St. Mary's (15) 1945 (Box-folder 71-53)
- Boonsboro--Trinity (16) 1945 (Box-folder 71-54)
- Bristol--Emmanuel (17) 1945 (Box-folder 71-55)
- Brookneal (18) 1945 (Box-folder 71-56)
- Buchanan--Grace (19); Buchanan--Trinity (20) 1945 (Box-folder 71-57)
- Callaway--St. Peter's--history (20) 1945 (Box-folder 71-58)
- Buena Vista--Christ (21) 1945 (Box-folder 71-59)
- Callaway--St. Peter's (22) 1945 (Box-folder 71-60)
- Cambria--Emmanuel Chapel (22A) 1945 (Box-folder 71-61)
- Cambria--Emmanuel Chapel (22A) 1945 (Box-folder 71-62)
- Box 72 1945
- Christiansburg--St. Thomas (23) 1945 (Box-folder 72-1)
- Christiansburg--St. Thomas (23) 1945 (Box-folder 72-2)
- Clifford--St. Mark's--"The Bishop's Plan" 1945 (Box-folder 72-3)
- Clifford--St. Mark's (24) 1945 (Box-folder 72-4)
- Clifton Forge--St. Andrew's (25) 1945 (Box-folder 72-5)
- Covington--Emmanuel (27) 1945 (Box-folder 72-6)
- Covington--Grace (28) 1945 (Box-folder 72-7)
- Dante--St. Mark's (29) 1945 (Box-folder 72-8)
- Evington--Good Shepherd (32); Ferrum--St. John's (33) 1945 (Box-folder 72-9)
- Fincastle--St. Mark's (34) 1945 (Box-folder 72-10)
- Folly Mills--Good Shepherd (35) 1945 (Box-folder 72-11)
- Forest--St. Stephen's (37) 1945 (Box-folder 72-12)
- Glasgow--St. John's (40) 1945 (Box-folder 72-13)
- St. Paul RFD #1--Honey Branch Mission (40A) 1945 (Box-folder 72-14)
- Hot Springs--St. Luke (41); Lebanon--Mission (43) 1945 (Box-folder 72-15)
- Lexington--Robert E. Lee Memorial (44) 1945 (Box-folder 72-16)
- Lynchburg--Good Shepherd (46) 1945 (Box-folder 72-17)
- Lynchburg--Grace Memorial (47) 1945 (Box-folder 72-18)
- Lynchburg--St. John's (48) 1945 (Box-folder 72-19)
- Lynchburg--St. Paul's (49); Madison Heights--Emmanuel (50) 1945 (Box-folder 72-20)
- Marion--Christ Church (51) 1945 (Box-folder 72-21)
- Martinsville--Christ Church (52) 1945 (Box-folder 72-22)
- Martinsville--St. Paul's Mission (52A); Massies Mill--Grace (53) 1945 (Box-folder 72-23)
- Montvale--St. Mark's (55); Nora--St. Stephen's (57) 1945 (Box-folder 72-24)
- Norton--All Saints (58) 1945 (Box-folder 72-25)
- Norwood--Christ Church (59) 1945 (Box-folder 72-26)
- Pearisburg--Christ (60) 1945 (Box-folder 72-27)
- Pearisburg--Christ--Executive Board Meeting December 13--minutes (61) 1945 (Box-folder 72-28)
- Pedlar Mills--St. Luke's (61); Pocahontas--Christ Church (62) 1945 (Box-folder 72-29)
- Pulaski--Christ Church (64) 1945 (Box-folder 72-30)
- Radford--Grace Church (65) 1945 (Box-folder 72-31)
- Radford--Grace (65) 1945 (Box-folder 72-32)
- Richlands--Trinity (66) 1945 (Box-folder 72-33)
- Richlands--Trinity--history (66) 1945 (Box-folder 72-34)
- Roanoke--Christ Church (67); Roanoke--Christ (67--special) 1945 (Box-folder 72-35)
- Roanoke--St. John's (68) 1945 (Box-folder 72-36)
- Roanoke--St. John's--Men's Club (68A) 1945 (Box-folder 72-37)
- Roanoke--St. Peter's (70) 1945 (Box-folder 72-38)
- Roanoke--St. Peter's (70) 1945 (Box-folder 72-39)
- Rocky Mount--Trinity (71) 1945 (Box-folder 72-40)
- St. Paul--Grace House (72) 1945 (Box-folder 72-41)
- Salem--St. Paul's (74) 1945 (Box-folder 72-42)
- Saltville--St. Paul's (75); Schuyler--Christ Church (76) 1945 (Box-folder 72-43)
- Splashdam--Good Shepherd (78) 1945 (Box-folder 72-44)
- Staunton--Emmanuel (79) 1945 (Box-folder 72-45)
- Staunton--Trinity (800) 1945 (Box-folder 72-46)
- Tazewell--Stras Memorial (82) 1945 (Box-folder 72-47)
- Tazewell--Stras Memorial--history and news clippings (82) 1945 (Box-folder 72-48)
- Waynesboro-St. John's (84); Wytheville--St. John's (85) 1945 (Box-folder 72-49)
- A--general (87) 1945 (Box-folder 72-50)
- B--general (88) 1945 (Box-folder 72-51)
- C--general (89) 1945 (Box-folder 72-52)
- D--general (90); E--general (91) 1945 (Box-folder 72-53)
- F--general (92) 1945 (Box-folder 72-54)
- G--general (93) 1945 (Box-folder 72-55)
- H--general (94); I--general (95) 1945 (Box-folder 72-56)
- I--general (95) 1945 (Box-folder 72-57)
- J--general (96); L--general (98) 1945 (Box-folder 72-58)
- M--general (99) 1945 (Box-folder 72-59)
- R--general (103) 1945 (Box-folder 72-60)
- S--general (104) 1945 (Box-folder 72-61)
- S--general (104) 1945 (Box-folder 72-62)
- T--general (105); U-V--general (106) 1945 (Box-folder 72-63)
- W--general (107) 1945 (Box-folder 72-64)
- X-Y-Z--general (108) 1945 (Box-folder 72-65)
- Anthony, Kenneth H., Reverend (111) 1945 (Box-folder 72-66)
- Army and Navy Commission (112) 1945 (Box-folder 72-67)
- Benson, Carl--Mint Spring (112A) 1945 (Box-folder 72-68)
- "The Bishop's Plan" (118) 1945 (Box-folder 72-69)
- "The Bishop's Plan" (118) 1945 (Box-folder 72-70)
- "The Bishop's Plan" (118) 1945 (Box-folder 72-71)
- Boys' Home--Covington (119) 1945 (Box-folder 72-72)
- Chancellor of Diocese (120) 1945 (Box-folder 72-73)
- Church Pension Fund (121) 1945 (Box-folder 72-74)
- Church Pension Fund--re. individual clergymen--closed (121C) 1945 (Box-folder 72-75)
- Church School Lenten Offering (122) 1945 (Box-folder 72-76)
- Church Society for College Work (122B) 1945 (Box-folder 72-77)
- Clergy Conference (124) 1945 (Box-folder 72-78)
- Consents (129) 1945 (Box-folder 72-79)
- Clerical Support (133) 1945 (Box-folder 72-80)
- Box 73 1945
- Council--constitution and canons (134) 1945 (Box-folder 73-1)
- Council--elections and credentials (136) 1945 (Box-folder 73-2)
- Council--general (138) 1945 (Box-folder 73-3)
- Council--hospitality (139) 1945 (Box-folder 73-4)
- Council--hospitality (139) 1945 (Box-folder 73-5)
- Council--new parishes and missions (143) 1945 (Box-folder 73-6)
- Council--program (145) 1945 (Box-folder 73-7)
- Council--reports (146) 1945 (Box-folder 73-8)
- Council--Secretary (148) 1945 (Box-folder 73-9)
- Depositions (151) 1945 (Box-folder 73-10)
- Diocesan Office (153) 1945 (Box-folder 73-11)
- Diocese--outside of (154) 1945 (Box-folder 73-12)
- Elliot Addressing Machine (155A) 1945 (Box-folder 73-13)
- Episcopal High School (156) 1945 (Box-folder 73-14)
- Episcopal High School (156) 1945 (Box-folder 73-15)
- Examining Chaplains (159) 1945 (Box-folder 73-16)
- Pledges for 1945 (163) 1945 (Box-folder 73-17)
- Treasurer's Statement--diocesan expenses and Field Department (164) 1945 (Box-folder 73-18)
- Executive Board--Department of Promotion (165) 1945 (Box-folder 73-19)
- Executive Board--promotion--Thomas A. Scott (165A) 1945 (Box-folder 73-20)